This is a little song about
About my glorious king (LeBron)
Yeah, all I think when I see someone sinking a three
I'm like, "That's Bron" (ooh ooh oh)
You're the king, all I need, everything in-between
Yeah you're LeBron, yeah you're Le-le-Bron
Said "if he was younger he'd still have hunger"
Ooh, now ain't that some shit (ain't that some shh)
'Cause although that pain in his leg, he's still trying his best
Yeah he's LeBron (ooh oh oh)
Bronny, you know you got you an army
We'll do anything to get you there
'Cause you're more an Xbox, and Jodan's more Atari
Ooh, the way you play your game ain't fair
No one better than you
I know you know it too, oh-oh-oh, yeah
Can't ever lose
LeBron that's the truth, oh-oh-oh, yeah
You're all I think when I see someone sinking a three
I'm like, "That's Bron" (ooh ooh oh)
You're the king, all I need, everything in-between
Yeah you're LeBron, yeah you're Le-le-Bron
Said "if he was younger he'd still have hunger"
Ooh, now ain't that some shit (ain't that some shh)
'Cause although that pain in his leg, he's still trying his best
Yeah he's LeBron (ooh oh oh)